K-Kagari?
（鈴羽(すずは)）か… かがり　待て！
Wait!
（鈴羽）あっ…
ハァ… ハァ…
う～ん
Kagari...
かがり…
Where is it?
（かがり）どこにあるの？
The precious gift... Mommy gave me.
ママからもらった大事な物
Precious gift, huh?
大事な物… か
（鈴羽）あっ…
Big Sis Rumi...
ルミ姉さん
（フェイリス）エヘッ
Well, meow?
（フェイリス）どうニャ？
Hmm... I've got maybe a week left.
（鈴羽）うん
やっぱり もって１週間かな
Feel bad for the others, though.
みんなには悪いけど
Suzu-meow, what's that?
鈴(すず)ニャン それは？
Ah...
（鈴羽）ああ
これは私の宝物なんだ
This is a treasure of mine.
Oh, is that you?!
Which means the one next to you is...
（フェイリス）
わあ これ 鈴ニャン？
とすると横の人は…
（鈴羽）うん
Yup. It's a photo with Mom.
母さんとの写真
（フェイリス）あっ…
Why do you look so grumpy in the picture, meow?
鈴ニャンは何で
こんな困り顔で写ってるニャ？
To be honest, I don't really remember.
（鈴羽）あまり よく
覚えてはいないんだけど…
Yeah, I don't remember...
（鈴羽）そう 覚えてない
By now, I've forgotten...
今は もう思い出せない
あ… 鈴ニャン
Suzu-meow...
（由季(ゆき)）あら
（鈴羽）あっ…
Oh?
Uh, Mo—Yuki?
母… あっ 由季さん
It's been a while.
（由季）お久しぶり
My brother?
（鈴羽）兄さん… ですか？
He's doing all right, I guess.
まあ 元気にしてますけど
Oh, I'm glad to hear it.
（由季）ああ だったらいいんです
I haven't heard from him at all lately,
最近 全然 連絡ないから
もしかしたら―
so I wondered if he's feeling
under the weather or something.
体調でも崩したんじゃないかって
気になって
I see... Well, if he's fine, that's good.
そっか… うん 元気ならいいんです
～
（まゆり）
真帆(まほ)さん 久しぶりだねえ
I can't wait to see Maho.
（岡部(おかべ)）見逃すなよ
Try not to miss her. Don't forget she's so...
何せ 相手は…
（フェイリス）あっ
Hiyajo.
（岡部）比屋定(ひやじょう)さん
（フェイリス）エヘヘ アハハッ
（真帆）お久しぶり みんな
Long time no see, you guys.
Marbled
Pork-Cutlet
Chicken
& Rice
（まゆり）真帆さん 元気そうだね
Maho seems to be doing well.
（岡部）ああ 教授の手伝いで
来日と言っていたけど―
Yeah, apparently she came to help the Professor.
What a busy girl.
しばらくは忙しそうだ
（まゆり）かがりちゃん
元気にしてるかなあ
I wonder if Kagari is doing well too?
Me too. I know Daru and
Suzuha were looking for her...
俺も…
ダルと鈴羽も捜しているんだが
（まゆり）うん
Yeah...
By the way, where's Hashida?
そういえば橋田(はしだ)さんは？
I guess he had something important to talk
with Suzu-meow about, so he couldn't come.
何か鈴ニャンと
大事な話があるとかで―
急に来れなくなったニャ
Hmm...
（真帆）ん…
CRT Television Workshop
ghjfdkslytureieow
何やってんだよ 父さん！
What the hell, Dad?!
Wh-What's that scary face for?
（ダル）ど どしたん？
そんな怖い顔して
Put your hand on your heart and think about it.
（鈴羽）自分の胸に手を当てて
考えてみて
Hand on my heart?
胸に手を？
ああっ
（鈴羽）んん…
If you keep doing crap like that,
Mom's really gonna get taken by somebody else!
そんなことばかりやってると―
ホントに母さんを
ほかの人に取られちゃうんだから！
Eh? Say again? What do you mean?
え？　何それ
どゆこと？
I saw it...
私 見たんだ
I saw Mom talking all friendly
with some other guy.
母さんが知らない男の人と
楽しそうに話してるとこ
Miss Amane was?
阿万音(あまね)氏が？
When's the last time you saw Mom?
最近 母さんと会ったのは？
Um, when I went to visit Miss Fubuki...
えっと…
フブキ氏のお見舞いのとき？
Since then?
それ以降は？
（ダル）ううん…
Why don't you meet her more often?!
何で もっと会っておかないの！
B-Because! I've been so busy
with the time leap machine and stuff...
（ダル）だ だって―
タイムリープマシンの件とかで
いろいろ忙しかったし…
You could find the time if you wanted to!
（鈴羽）
時間は自分で作るものだろう？
うっ… サーセン
Sorry...
What if this keeps up and
Mom ends up marrying someone else?
もし このまま母さんが
別の人と結婚したりしたら…
Hmm... Maybe it's no big deal?
（ダル）う～ん
まっ でも大丈夫じゃね？
It was probably just some guy asking
for directions or trying to sell her something.
その男の人ってのも―
道を聞かれてたとか
お店の勧誘とかだよ きっと
And if it wasn't?
（鈴羽）もし違ったら？
If you're that worried about it,
why don't you just go and ask her?
そんなに気になるんなら
本人に確かめればよかったじゃん
How come you're not the least bit concerned?!
何で父さんは
そんなに余裕なんだよ！
もしかしたら―
At this rate, I might never
end up being born in the future!
私が生まれてこない未来に
なってしまうかもしれないんだぞ
But doesn't the fact that you're here
right now mean you'll be born for sure?
でも 今 ここに
鈴羽がいるってことはさ
生まれてくるってことじゃね？
Hmm?
ん？　これって…
Is that... Miss Amane from the future?!
未来の阿万音氏？
おおっ ロリ鈴羽もラブリー！
Ooh! Loli Suzuha is lovely!
That isn't the point! Look closer!
そうじゃなくて よく見て！
（ダル）え？
Eh?
Why are you so faded out?
鈴羽 何か薄くね？
It's been like this for a while now.
（鈴羽）この前から
こんなふうなんだ
That's just like Back to the—
こ これは バック･トゥ･ザ…
Dad!
（鈴羽）父さん！
Wh-What?
な 何？
（鈴羽）父さんは自信がないんだな
（ダル）え？
You have zero confidence, Dad.
It's because you lack confidence
that instead of making the first move,
自分に自信がないから 自分から
アプローチしようとせず
you're waiting and hoping for her to.
向こうから来てくれるのを
待ってるんだ
違う？
Am I wrong?
あっ うっ それは…
That's...
No future awaits those
who refuse to take action.
（鈴羽）“自ら行動しない者に
未来は訪れない”
え？
Eh?
That's something you
told me a long time ago, Dad.
（鈴羽）昔 父さんが
私に教えてくれた言葉だよ
I said all that?
僕がそんなことを？
えっ でもさ…
But, that's—
Listen to me!
とにかく！　私としては―
If you and Mom aren't getting along,
I might be in trouble! I mean it!
父さんと母さんが
うまくいってくれないと困るんだ
だから！
（まゆり）トゥットゥルー
ただいまー
We're here!
あれ？
Huh?
Ruka and Moeka too?
るか君に萌郁(もえか)さんも？
What's going on here?
どうしたの？　一体
Big Sis Mayu...
（鈴羽）まゆ姉さん
（ダル）うっ うう…
We're going to need your help.
力を貸してほしいんだ
Eh?
えっ？
Um, so... Before their date tomorrow,
（まゆり）えーっと つまり…
あしたのデートまでに―
you want Daru to learn
how to have confidence in himself?
ダル君が自分に自信を持てるように
すればいいってこと？
（鈴羽）うん
私 そういうの うといから
I'm no good at things like that,
which is why I need everybody's help.
だから
みんなに協力してほしいんだ
Did you use that photo, meow?
例の写真 使ったのニャ？
（鈴羽）エヘッ
Big Bro!
（鈴羽）兄さん
（ダル）はっ はい！
Y-Yes?!
Our mission will now commence!
ただいまよりミッションを開始する
The operation objective:
Concluding their date tomorrow,
なお 本ミッションは
明日(みょうにち)のデートにおける―
Hashida Itaru will confront Amane Yuki
and confess his feelings for her.
橋田 至(いたる)による阿万音由季への
告白を最終目的とする
C-Confess?!
こっ 告白!?　んなムチャな…
That's crazy talk!
口答えは必要ない！　返事は？
That's not what I want to hear! Try again!
Miss Suzuha! Yes, ma'am! Miss Suzuha!
鈴様！　はい！　鈴様！
The poor girl wanted to see you so badly that
she was begging "Let me come to Japan too!"
（レスキネン）いやあ
どうしても君に会いたいから―
“自分も日本に来させろ！”と
聞かなくてね
I said no such thing.
（真帆）そんなこと言ってません
（岡部）アッハハハ…
By the way, Lintahlo... How is that report
we discussed the other day coming along?
（レスキネン）
ところで リンターロ
先日 話していた
レポートの件だけど―
（真帆）あっ
どうなっているかな？
Well, I have it right here.
ああ それならここに
Oho? You impress me.
（レスキネン）ほう 感心だね
Maho!
Help me!
（真帆）ん… 鈴羽さん？
Suzuha?
It's nothing special, but here it is.
（岡部）出来は
どうだか分かりませんが…
Lintahlo.
（レスキネン）リンターロ
（岡部）あ…
Modesty isn't always a good virtue in practice.
（レスキネン）
謙遜は必ずしも美徳じゃないよ
フン
特にアメリカでやっていくならね
Especially if you're hoping
to go far in America.
（岡部）あ…
すみませ…
Sorry, I mean...
あ いえ ありがとうございます
Thank you.
うん それでは このレポートは―
I'll have to put aside some time tonight
to sit back and read this report of yours.
今晩にでも
じっくり読ませてもらおう
If it's good enough, you might be
able to transfer before you know it.
出来によっては 留学も
即 現実になるかもしれないよ
はい
Great.
And I'm sure Maho would love that too.
そうなったら
真帆もうれしいだろう
う… 教授！
Professor!
アハハ…
Incoming Call
Mayuri
What's up?
（岡部）どうした？
Ah, Okarin?
（まゆり）あっ オカリン？
Um, a bunch of us are gathered at the lab right now,
so I was wondering if you wanted to join us?
あのね 今 みんなで
ラボに集まってるんだけど―
よかったら
オカリンもどうかなって
At the lab?
ラボに？
Yeah... Will you come?
（まゆり）うん どうかな？
あ… すまない
Sorry...
Maybe another time.
悪いけど また
I see... Okay, no problem!
そっか
うん 分かった ごめんね
That's too bad. Keep it up, Okarin!
頑張ってね オカリン
（ダル）う… うう…
If you wanna be a popular guy, you've gotta
know all the tasty places to go, meow!
（フェイリス）モテる男の条件！
それは おいしいお店を
知ってることだニャ
So without further ado, we'll be drilling good
restaurants and manners into your head, meow!
というわけで―
今からフェイリスが
いいお店と―
そこでのマナーについて
たたき込むニャ！
Miss Faris! Yes, ma'am! Miss Faris!
フェイリス様！
はい！　フェイリス様！
Yuki is a huge cosplayer, right?
由季さんは
コスプレーヤーさんだよね
だから―
So, I'm thinking if you wear
something different than usual,
いつもとは
違う服装だったりすると―
it might make her heart flutter, you know?
ちょっとドキッとしちゃうかもだね
Miss Mayuri! Yes, ma'am! Miss Mayuri!
まゆり様！　はい！　まゆり様！
To be honest, the most important thing
is to understand a woman's heart.
（るか）やっぱり…
女の子の気持ちに
なってあげることが大切かと
Keep the conversation
fun and exciting.
うあ～
Well, Big Bro?
（鈴羽）どう 兄さん
少しは自信ついた？
Feeling confident yet?
Huh? Uh, yeah...
（ダル）え？　あ まあ…
I can't believe you had me come here for this...
（真帆）人が何事かと思って
来てみたら…
You're kidding me, right?
何なのよ これ
Maho! Where's Okarin?
（まゆり）真帆さん！
オカリンは？
The professor made me leave without him.
（真帆）
教授に押しつけてきたわよ
Will you help us?
（鈴羽）手伝ってくれるの？
It's a pain for me too
if Hashida stays like this.
（真帆）橋田さんが
この状態なのは 私も困るし
（まゆり）ん？
Fill me in on the details.
詳しく話を聞かせてちょうだい
Actually...
（鈴羽）実は…
In other words, he needs more
confidence dealing with women.
（真帆）要するに女性に対して
自信がつけばいいのよね？
What's that?
（鈴羽）これは？
For now, let's just say an experimental
system with an improvement or two.
（真帆）以前 実験的に
作ってみたシステムの―
改良版とでも言っておくわ
But basically, it's something
of a sleep-learning device.
まあ 要するに
睡眠学習装置のようなものよ
（鈴羽）ああ…
Hashida Itaru.
橋田 至
Believe it or not, you're a lady's man.
あなたは本当はデキる男よ
えっ？
Not even Don Juan could compare
to your charm and success.
あなたはドン･ジョバンニも
びっくりの希代のいい男なの
I-I'm a successful man...
（ダル）ぼ… 僕はいい男
Now...
（真帆）さあ 目覚めなさい
Open your eyes.
（由季）ウフッ
Yuki.
（ダル）由季さん
（由季）あっ
（ダル）フッ
Hashida?
橋田… さん？
Bring the usual.
（ダル）いつものを
（店員）かしこまりました
Very well.
You come here that often?
いつも こんな所に？
ハハハハ… 僕はデキる男ですから
Because I'm a successful man.
R-Right...
は はあ…
Was that any good?
あれでよろしかったですか？
Perfect, meow!
バッチリニャン
I don't know... Do you think it's going well?
どうかなあ うまくいってるかなあ
It has to be! I know it!
うまくいってるよ 絶対に
Maho-meow's idea is sure paying off big time!
それにしても
真帆ニャンの暗示 すっごいニャ
Well, I never thought it'd be so effective...
いや でも まさか
あんなに効くなんて
Wow! This is beautiful!
（由季）わあ～
きれいですね
ああ でも―
It is, but...
You're even more beautiful.
君のほうがきれいさ
あ… ありがとうございます
Thank you...
What a romantic mood!
（まゆり）いい雰囲気だねえ
（鈴羽）あとは最後の一撃を
決めるだけだ 兄さん！
All that's left is for Big Bro
to deliver the final blow!
（フェイリス）あっ 見るニャ
Look, meow!
Um, today was—
あの 今日は…
Yuki.
（ダル）由季さん
（由季）あっ えっと…
Umm, Hashida?
は… 橋田さん？
I have something to say, Yuki.
（ダル）聞いてください 由季さん
Uh...
（由季）あの…
（ダル）由季さん
Yuki, will you...
僕は…
わあ… あっ
Will you...
僕と…
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
Recognition
of the
Asymptotic
Line
Recognize
Asymptote
I failed...
（ダル）失敗した
Dad, get a hold of yourself.
父さん しっかりしてよ
It's not like you were rejected, right?
まだフラれたって
決まったわけじゃないだろ
No matter how you look at it,
she's gotta hate me, noob!
（ダル）あれは どう考えても
嫌われただろ 常考(じょうこう)
Will you...
（ダル）僕と…
Oh no... Look at the time...
（由季）いけない もうこんな時間
（ダル）えっ？
Eh?
I need to get going.
私 帰らなきゃ
Huh?!
ああっ
I had so much fun today. Thank you.
（由季）今日は楽しかったです
ありがとうございました
（鈴羽たち）ああ…
Uh...
I knew it was pointless...
（ダル）やっぱ阿万音氏は
僕みたいな男に誘われても―
Deep down inside, she doesn't
want to be asked out by a guy like me.
内心 迷惑だったんだお
But I was all cocky and misread the situation
and had the nerve to hold her hand...
それなのに僕ってば勘違いして
調子に乗っちゃって
手なんか握っちゃったりして
Yeah, and just look at my body...
My hands are sticky and sweaty and nasty.
ほら 僕って この体形だから―
手汗とか いっぱいかきまくりの
ベタベタだし
I bet she was thinking to herself...
彼女だって きっと心の中で―
Eww! Disgusting! Let go of
my hand already, you slimy pervert!
“キモイ ウザイ”
“離せ ヘンタイ”って
思ってたに違いないんだお
No! Mom's not that kind of person!
（鈴羽）違う！
母さんは そんな人じゃ…
（ダル）最初から
変だと思ってたんだよね
I knew it was too good
to be true from the start...
だってさ
あんなかわいい おにゃのこが―
Think about it! Why would such a cute
girl ever decide to marry a guy like me?!
僕みたいな男の
お嫁さんになってくれるなんて―
That just doesn't happen, it's common sense!
常識的に考えて
あるわけないじゃん
Miss Amane will end up with somebody else...
やっぱ阿万音氏は別の人と…
（鈴羽）なっ…
そんなわけないだろ 父さん！
Don't say stuff like that, Dad!
But you're the one who said it was happening...
（ダル）でも最初に
そう言ったのは鈴羽じゃん
Dad...
父さん？
（ダル）ごめん
ちょっと１人にしておくれ
Sorry, but I need some time alone...
あっ…
Suzu, I'm sorry.
鈴さん ごめんね
（鈴羽）まゆ姉さん
Big Sis Mayu...
No, this all happened
because I doctored that photo.
ううん 元はと言えばフェイリスが
あんな写真 作ったから
私もやりすぎたわ
I went too far as well...
No...
違うよ 悪いのは…
It's not your fault...
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
It's my fault.
（鈴羽）私のせい
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Yeah...
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
そうだ あのときも…
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Karaoke
One Person
Rooms!
The Best
Game Center
Just like then...
Mom! Mom!
（鈴羽）母さん！　母さん！
Suzuha!
（由季）鈴羽！
（鈴羽）えっ？
Watch out!
（由季）危ない！
（鈴羽）あっ 母…
M-Mom?
母さ…
うあーっ！
（鈴羽）父さん
Dad?
Could we talk maybe?
少し いいかな？
Yeah.
（ダル）うん
（鈴羽）私がいた未来ではさ
The future that I came from...
It wasn't such a peaceful world.
平和な世の中なんて
なかったから
I never spent much time together with
you and Mom. There wasn't a chance to.
父さんと母さんと
一緒にいる時間なんて―
ほとんどなかったんだ
So...
だから…
The truth is...
本当はさ
ただ見たかっただけなんだ
I just wanted to see it.
自分を産んでくれた
母さんと父さんの―
My mom and dad who gave
birth to me, getting along together...
仲よくしているところを
That way, I'd feel like
I'm heading down the right path.
そうすれば これから
私が目指す道が間違ってない―
I thought that'd be the proof I needed...
そう確信できるんじゃないかって
I'm sorry.
ごめんね
知らない男の人とってのも
私が消えちゃうってのもウソなんだ
Her talking to some other guy
and me disappearing was a lie.
I lied to you.
私が父さんに…
Well, I kinda figured you were.
（ダル）
まあ 何となくは分かってた
え？
Huh?
Yeah, I knew...
（ダル）分かるよ うん
Dad...
（鈴羽）父さん…
It doesn't matter if you
were lying or telling the truth.
（ダル）ホントかウソか
そんなことは どうでもよくてさ
I just... wanted someone
to give me that push on the back.
僕も誰かに背中を
押してほしかったんだと思う
I was being selfish.
甘えてしまったんだよね
I'm the one who needs to apologize.
だから謝るのは僕のほうだ
父さん
Dad...
Miss Amane?
（ダル）あっ 阿万音氏？
今日は その ごめん
Sorry about today.
Yeah, so hey...
うん それでさ
Tomorrow, do you want
to meet up with me again?!
あした もう一回だけ
会ってくんないかな
あっ…
Yeah... Yeah, yeah.
（ダル）うん うんうん
Later.
それじゃ
Yuki
Call Completed
フッ
Yuki
Call Completed
Dad...
（鈴羽）父さん…
父さんには かなわないな
I can't compete with you, Dad.
（真帆）ハァ…
Good grief...
あ～ もう
What the heck am
I supposed to do all on my own?
私１人で どうしろっていうのよ
（ダル）阿万音氏！
（由季）あっ
Miss Amane!
ヘヘッ
Today was lots of fun. Thank you.
（由季）今日は楽しかったです
ありがとうございました
Right back at you. Thanks for
hanging out with me two days in a row.
（ダル）こちらこそ２日も連続で
つきあってもらっちゃって
ん… 阿万音氏？
Miss Amane?
Personally, I think you're wonderful
when you act like yourself.
やっぱりいつもの橋田さんのほうが
すてきだと思います
あ…
え…
えっ…
Uh, um...
あ… その…
Dad...
父さん…
I-I...
（ダル）ぼ 僕は…
I think of you and feel...
僕は君に一生
萌(も)え萌えキュンだおー！
...Moe Moe Kyun!
Dad...
父さん
あっ…
フッ フフ…
ハハハッ…
Thank goodness...
（鈴羽）よかった これで もう…
With this, I can...
ん… あっ
Think we can meet today?
There's so much I
want to talk about.
Think we can meet today?
There's so much I want to talk about.
（まゆり）
“今日 会えないかな？”
“話したいこと
たくさんあるんだ”
（岡部）フッ…
（レスキネン）リンターロ
Lintahlo. Sorry to keep you.
待たせたね
Oh, no. It's okay.
（岡部）あっ いえ 大丈夫です
Forgive me. Work at the hospital
has been one problem after another.
すまないね 病院のほうの仕事も
なかなか煩雑でね
But I did look over your report.
レポートは読ませてもらったよ
There are a few areas that need polishing up,
but your viewpoint and ideas are interesting.
いろいろ粗削りなところはあるが
着眼と発想はおもしろい
Do you have time to stay
and answer some questions about it?
いくつか内容について
質問させてもらっていいかな？
Sure, that's fine with me.
（岡部）はい もちろん構いません
Your brother cares for you very much.
（由季）妹思いの
いいお兄さんですね
Yeah... I couldn't wish for a better family.
（鈴羽）うん 私の最高の家族だよ
So, my brother...
その… 兄のこと
これからも よろしくお願いします
Please take good care of him.
Me too.
私も…
Itaru makes me
Moe Moe Kyun too, you know?
至さんに 萌え萌えキュン！
なんですよ
あ…
Suzuha... I'm so happy I gave birth to you...
（由季）鈴羽…
あなたが生まれてくれてよかった
Thank you.
ありがとう
H-Huh?
あれ？　おかしいな
This is weird...
I'm... Why am I...?
私 何で…
あっ…
It's okay. You don't have to say anything.
いいのよ
何も言わなくて
Aren't you going to be in it?
（鈴羽）兄さんは入らないの？
It's fine, it's fine!
（ダル）いいの いいの
Her and I will take plenty together from now on.
僕たちは これから
いくらでも撮れるからさ
I'm taking it.
ほいじゃ いくよ
（鈴羽）あっ…
（由季）ウフフ
（由季）本当にいいの？
Are you sure?
If I keep bugging you two any longer,
I'll feel like a third wheel.
さすがに これ以上
２人の邪魔をしたら―
私が馬に蹴られちゃうよ
フフッ じゃ 行こうか
（由季）はい
Shall we?
Okay.
Thank you, Mom...
（鈴羽）ありがとう 母さん
～